Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Smith Papers, 1887-1976; 3; 62 document boxes, 2 oversized boxes, and 3 oversized folders.
  - Correspondence, 1914-1975; 1
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1953 December-1954 December (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1955 January-1956 February (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Gloria Painter Smith, 1956 May-1957 October (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1957-1959 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Family: Paul Bagby Smith and Alba Ferrer Smith, 1972-1974 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1945, 1948-1952 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1953 March-September (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1953 September-1954 July (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1954 July-November (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1954 November-1955 January (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1955 February-April (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1955 April-July (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1955 August-1956 May (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1956 May-June (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1956 July-November (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1956 December-1957 December (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Family: Thelma Lou Smith, 1959 January-November (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1960 April-1961 March (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1961 May-November (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1961 November-1962 July (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1962 August-1963 March (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1963 March-December (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1964 June-December (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1965 January-1966 February (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1966 March-July (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1966 September-1967 March (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1967 April-November (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1967 December-1968 May (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1968 June-December (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1968 December-1969 March (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1969 April-August (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Family: William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1970-1972, 1975, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1934-1935, 1939, 1942-1943 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1943 March-April (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1943 May-September (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1943 October (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1943 November (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1943 November-1944 January (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 January-February (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 February (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 February-March (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 March-April (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 April-May (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 June (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 July-October (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 October (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1944 November-1945 January (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith, 1945-1946 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Family: Helen Frances Smith and Jimmye Standard Hillman, 1947 January-May (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1947 August-1948 April (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1948 May-August (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1948 September-1949 January (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1949 February-May (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1949 June-September (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1949 October-December (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1950 January-June (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1950 July-1951 February (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1951 March-September (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1951 November-1952 April (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1952 May-September (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1952 October-1953 June (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1953 July-December (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1954 January-April (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1954 May-September (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1954 September-1955 February (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1955 March-July (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1955 August-September (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1955 November-1956 March (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1956 April-September (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1956 October-1957 February (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1957 March-May (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1957 June-November (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1957 December-1958 May (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1958 June-August (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1958 August-1959 January (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1959 February-June (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1959 July-December (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1960 January-April (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1960 June-September (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1960 September-1961 May (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1961 June-December (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1962 January-August (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1962 September-December (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1963 January-September (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1963 October-December (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1964 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1964 February-July (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1964 August-October (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1964 November-1965 January (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1965 February-June (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1965 July-1966 January (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1966 February-May (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1966 June-September (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1966 October-1967 February (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1967 April-August (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1967 September-October (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1967 November-December (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1968 January-June (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1968 July-December (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1969 February-August (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1969 September-December (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1970 January-March (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1970 April-July (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1970 August-November (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1970 December-1971 April (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1971 May-August (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1971 September-1972 February (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1972 March-May (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1972 June-November (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1972 December-1974 January (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Family: Jimmye Standard Hillman and Helen Frances Smith Hillman, 1974 February-1975 September, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Family: Riette and C. Richard Voges, 1932-1933 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Family: Riette and C. Richard Voges, 1953-1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Family: Nellie Buck, 1918-1962, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Blank Postcards: (1 of 12), undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Blank Postcards: (2 of 12), undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Blank Postcards: (3 of 12), undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Blank Postcards: (4 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Blank Postcards: (5 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Blank Postcards: (6 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Blank Postcards: (7 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Blank Postcards: (8 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Blank Postcards: (9 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Blank Postcards: (10 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Blank Postcards: (11 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Blank Postcards: (12 of 12), undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1944-1950 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1944-1950 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1944-1950 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1951-1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1951-1960 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1951-1960 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1951-1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1961-1969 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1961-1969 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - From Alice Bagby Smith, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - To and from Harley Smith, 1968-1975 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - To and from Harley Smith, 1948-1960 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - To and from Harley Smith, 1948-1960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - To and from Harley Smith (1 of 2), 1961-1967 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - To and from Harley Smith (2 of 2), 1961-1967 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1922-1923 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1923-1924 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1924-1925 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1924-1926 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1925 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1925 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1925 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1925 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1925-1926 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1926 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1926 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1926 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1926 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 6), 1927 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 6), 1927 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 6), 1927 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 6), 1927 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 6), 1927 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 6), 1927 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1928 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1930 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 6), 1931 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 6), 1931 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 6), 1931 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 6), 1931 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 6), 1931 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 6), 1931 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1932 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1932 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1932 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1932 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1933 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1933 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1933 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 15), 1934 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (11 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (12 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (13 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (14 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (15 of 15), 1934 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (11 of 17), 1935 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (12 of 17), 1935 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (13 of 17), 1935 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (14 of 17), 1935 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (15 of 17), 1935 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (16 of 17), 1935 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (17 of 17), 1935 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 10), 1936 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 10), 1937 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 10), 1937 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 7), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 9), 1939 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 9), 1939 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1940 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1940 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1940 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1940 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 7), 1941 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 7), 1941 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 7), 1941 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 7), 1941 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 7), 1941 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 7), 1941 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 7), 1941 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (11 of 11), 1942 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 6), 1943 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 6), 1943 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 6), 1943 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 6), 1943 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 6), 1943 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 6), 1943 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 5), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 7)